# Reema N Gowda

reemagowdan@gmail.com https://github.com/reema-gowda

	_	

$\ \square$ Full Stack Development (MEAN Stack: MongoDB, Express.js, ReactJS, Node.js) $\ \square$
JavaScript 🛮 Saas 🖟 JIRA 🖟 APIs 🖺 HTML 5 🗍 CSS 3 🖟 Git 🖺 Heroku 🖟
Collaboration

### **Summary**

Full-Stack Web developer able to build a Web presence from the ground up from concept, navigation, layout and programming. Skilled at writing well-designed, efficient code using current best practices in Web development. Self driven and goal-oriented professional committed To build websites with rich user experience

## **Experience**

Full-Stack Software Student BrainStation January 2019 - April 2019 Coding Bootcamp Toronto.

□ Capstone Project - Meme-dream - Full-Stack Project -skills : Express js, Node js, React, javascript, Html, Css3, SendGrid , Web Api, Npm Package, React Router DOM
It's a free online image maker that allows you to add custom resizable text to images user will able to download the picture and save to their local, and user will able to email owner of the project to get in touch this done by implementing the SENDGRID.
☐ <b>Group Projec</b> t - <b>InStock Collaborative Full Stack Projec</b> t- Skills- React Router DOM, Node js, React , Html , CSS3
☐ Worked with a team of developers to create a mobile-first application A financial

analysis tool using moving averages.

□ Coding Challenge - Bitcoin - Skill: Node js, React , Html ,Css3.
Blockcyphers API to return the balance of a specific bitcoin testnet address and
also make a payment using testnet bitcoins. Were i got free Bitcoin from faucet for $% \left( 1\right) =\left( 1\right) \left( 1\right) $

### **Previous Experience**

Technical Talent Acquisition Specialist March 2015 - Oct 2017, BANGALORE, INDIA

- Roles and Responsibilities:
- Involved in complete end to end recruitment life cycle for permanent Staffing.

testing purposes only and created transaction using node js.

- Responsibilities include calling candidates, posting of requirements on job portals, sourcing, screening and
- evaluation of resumes, salary negotiations and sending the best resume at the client side.
- Recruiting involves creating complex Boolean search strings, social networking sites such as LinkedIn and
- various job boards that are in the market.
- Clients handled; IBM(GBS).

#### Education

- Full Stack Software Full time Diploma program BrainStation January 2019 to April 2019 Coding Bootcamp Toronto [] Completed an 13-week immersive full-stack software program.
- Hacker-you Part time web development program Toronto- 2018.
- Christ University / Master in computer Application June 2011 March 2014, Bangalore, India.
- Christ University / Bachelor of Science June 2009 March 2011, Bangalore.India.